Thiago Loureiro de Azevedo

Nationality: Portuguese | Date of birth: 31 /1 /1984 | Location: Malta

t +356 9965 1330



thiagoguaru@me.com

Technical Blog: Github: **Projects and more:**

https://medium.com/@thiagoloureiro/ https://github.com/thiagoloureiro http://www.thiagoloureiro.com.br/

With over eleven years' experience in software development, my work includes everything from simple Console/Windows Forms applications to large systems for process control, institutional systems, integration with ERP systems, Windows Forms, ASP.NET, Windows Mobile, Xamarin Apps, .NET Core, WebAPIs.

I take a critical look and see if the project's premises and objectives are consistent, if the choices made will not have undesirable side effects and if there are more efficient. I consider it essential to be committed to quality and delivery time, always devoting all my effort to the companies for which I work. All this, of course, maintaining professional and ethical conduct.

Programming Languages and Applications

Languages: Asp.Net, C#, VB, VBA, SQL, JavaScript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, GoLang

Applications and Tools: Visual Studio .Net, MicroServices Architecture, Consul.io, Hystrix.NET, CircuitBreaker Pattern, Microsoft Orleans, Actor Based Frameworks, Jira, TFS, VSTS, SQL Server, Windows Mobile/CE, Xamarin, Windows Forms, Reporting Services (SSRS), MySQL, Crystal Reports, MS Project, MS Office, Visual Studio Online, GIT, Scrum, Redis, RabbitMQ, NancyFX, Webservices, SignalR, WPF, WCF, Visual Studio Extensions

(SQL Server) Strong T-SQL Skills, Stored Procedures, Triggers, Assemblies, CLRs

S.O.L.I.D principles, Dependency Injection, Unit Tests, Nuget Packages

Experience

Senior .NET Full stack Developer

Company: Play'n GO Dates: Jan 2018 - Present

Location: Malta

PLAY'n

Orleans Framework, Game Development, development project templates, Visual Studio Extensions, WebAPI, .NET Standard, .NET Core, NancyFX

Senior .NET Full Stack Developer

Company: Lotto Direct Dates: Nov 2017 - Dec 2017

Location: Malta

Working with The Lotter software/site.

Micro services infrastructure development, C#, Hystrix, Consul, NancyFX, RabbitMQ, Redis, CQRS SQL

Server and Legacy Systems

Senior .NET Backend Developer

Company: Scheduit

Dates: Jul 2017 - Nov 2017

Location: Malta

Amico.ai Chatbot APP, Development of backend WebAPI, Entity Framework, Dapper, Caching (Redis),

Micro Services, Unit Tests, Integration Tests.

.NET Solutions Architect / SQL / MES Specialist

Company: IASTECH Automação de Sistemas

Dates: Oct 2006 - May 2017

Location: Brazil

Almost 11 years working as Full Stack Developer in an Agile Environment, more than 50 projects using .NET technologies, acting as Team Leader, Scrum Master, MES Specialist, Developer, Design Specifications, Perform Code Reviews, Documentation, and Testing.

Education

Degree:

2015 – Superior in Gestão em TI – Universidade Metropolitana de Santos

Courses:

- ✓ Administering a Microsoft SQL Server 2000 Database 2072
- ✓ Developing ASP.NET MVC 4 Web Application 20486
- ✓ Advanced Web Programming (ASP.NET 2.0) 2544
- ✓ Aspen InfoPlus.21: Applications Development Advanced 311
- ✓ Aspen InfoPlus.21: Real Time Information Management Foundation PME101
- ✓ Developing Microsoft ASP.NET Applications 2310
- ✓ GAMP 5
- ✓ Programming with C# 2124
- ✓ Querying Microsoft SQL Server 2000 with Transact-SQL 2071
- ✓ Rockwell Automation FT Historian
- ✓ Rockwell Automation FT Metrics

Languages

English: Full professional proficiency

Portuguese: Native



